CHRISTIAN PEREYRA

christian_p1996@hotmail.com

Montevideo, Uruguay

vCard:



Soporte técnico e infraestructura

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/christian-pereyra-bentos/

About Me:

Technician with 5 years of experience in IT support and infrastructure through tasks of server administration, mail, antivirus, to tasks closer to the user performing Helpdesk remote and Onsite. Always oriented to the satisfaction of the end user and clients fulfilling in time and form with the tasks, always trying to be focused on the continuous development of good results.

currently looking to transition career/position into software development.

EDUCATION

 Universidad del Trabajo del Uruguay - UTU Mar. 2016 – Dic. 2018 Montevideo, Uruguay.

Degree: Computer Science Baccalaureate

High School – Lyceum N° 9 IDEA
Montevideo, Uruguay.
Degree: Engineering

Career Summary

BASF Services Américas (Outsourcing) - Dic. 2020 – Until today

Montevideo, Uruguay.

Position: IT Support Analyst

Contracted by Datalogic Software SRL

Tasks:

- -Preparation and repair of PCs and other equipment for new and existing employees.
- -Onboarding of new employees about internal systems and information security awareness.
- -Support to existing employees onsite and remote.
- -Network cabling patching.
- Ordering and control of the hardware stock.

Nummi S.A. – REDPAGOS (Outsourcing) - Aug. 2019 – Feb. 2020

Position: Helpdesk Support

Contracted by AT SRL

Tasks:

- -Remote and On-Site user support for the different collection agencies.
- -Internal support: PC troubleshooting, mail, printers, networks, patching, telephony,
- -Windows 7 and 10 imaging with Sysprep and implementation through SCCM (System Center Configuration Manager).
- -Antivirus monitoring (Trend-Micro). Monitoring (Nagios).
- -Mail (Zimbra).
- -Repair of hardware of the equipment or sent to external services.
- -Contact with service providers of printers, PCs, general electronics.
- -Use of incident and task ticketing system with Workfront and GLPI software.

AT SRL Mar. 2019 – Feb. 2020

Montevideo, Uruguay.

Position: IT Support and basic infrastructure administration

Tasks:

- -Remote and On-Site support to end users.
- -Preventive maintenance (Checklist) in contract customers (Servers, Backups (Veeam), Antivirus (Kaspersky and Symantec).
- -Networking.
- -Preventive Monitoring Nagios and improvement actions and client infrastructure.

Installation of Windows 7 and Windows 10 Operating Systems.

Assignment and creation of users in mail platform (Office 365, Google Apps (GSuite) and Zimbra).

Administration and testing of Servers (Windows 2008 - 2012 - 2016).

Sonda Uruguay S.A.

Jun. 2018 - Feb. 2019

Montevideo, Uruguay.

Position: Field Support technician

Tasks:

- -Installation, diagnosis and On-Site configuration of PCs, notebooks, printers, network cabling.
- -PC and notebook repair and maintenance.
- -Installation and configuration of Microsoft Windows and Linux operating systems.
- -Fulfillment of SLA's contracted by the client and direct report to him of the completion of the task.
- -Contact with suppliers for equipment and supplies of PC's and printers.

Freelance: service repair at hardware and software

2015 - until today

I work in a particular way as a PC and cellular technician, totally oriented to the final public and with a clear vocation of service to be able to maintain my personal business.

Courses and Certifications

Azure Fundamentals

- -SQL Basics
- -Windows Server 2016 Administration
- -Microsoft Intune MDM
- -Microsoft SCCM and MECM
- -Azure Fundamentals
- -DevOps fundamentals
- -GCP Cloud fundamentals: Core Infrastructure
- -Google IT Support Specialist (5 courses)
- -Linux Administration Basics
- -Information Security (BIOS institute)
- -IBM Cybersecurity Analyst (ongoing)
- -Scrum Fundamentals
- -Fortinet NSE1
- -Fortinet NSE2 (ongoing)
- -Veeam Backup and Replication Basics

and more at my Github

References

Rodrigo Martínez: Senior Technical Support at Sonda Uruguay: 091 458 869

Diego Caggiano- IT Coordinator at BASF: 096 272 006 Sebastián Eizmendi – IT Analyst at BASF: 098 889 173